Fowler C. West papers, Inclusive: 1964-2009, Bulk: 1965-1993
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
Fowler C. West papers
Inclusive: 1964-2009, Bulk: 1965-1993
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials http://www.baylor.edu/lib/bcpm/
93
West, Fowler C., 1940 -
67 document boxes 4 three-ring binder boxes
The Fowler C. West papers represent West’s Washington, D.C. career, 1964-1993, on the U.S. House of Representatives Agriculture Committee staff and as Commissioner of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission. Records include correspondence, speeches, administrative files, and subject files among other items.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Average.
Biography/Profile
Fowler C. West was born July 6, 1940, in Bosqueville, Texas. He attended North Texas State University, 1958-1959, but received his BA degree in Political Science and History from Baylor University in 1963. He earned an MA from George Washington University in Legislative Affairs in 1980, and a JD degree from Georgetown University Law Center in 1988.
West began his government career in Washington, D.C. as a staff assistant in the office of Congressman W. R. Poage following his graduation from Baylor. From 1965 to 1969, he was on the professional staff of the House Committee on Agriculture where he had responsibilities involved with the Farm Bill of 1965 and the Laboratory Animal Welfare Act. Then, from 1969 to 1971, he served as Administrative Assistant to Poage acting as staff director and chief advisor.
In 1971, West returned to the House Committee on Agriculture as a staff consultant where he served as a legislative professional involved in the development and enactment of the Rural Development Act of 1972, the Farm Credit Act of 1971, and the Rural Telephone Bank Act of 1971. He was promoted to Staff Director of the Committee in 1973. As chief administrative officer of the Committee, he managed a staff of 50 professional and clerical employees and represented the Chairman in scheduling and processing of all legislative matters as well as organizing the Committee each session. During this period, the Committee developed several major legislative packages, including the Farm Bills of 1977 and 1981, and the Commodity Futures Trading Commission Act of 1974 which created the CFTC. He served under Committee Chairmen W. R. Poage, 1973-1974; Thomas S. Foley, 1975-1980; and Kika de la Garza, 1981-1982.
President Ronald Reagan appointed West a Commissioner of the CFTC in 1982 for a 5-year term. As a Commissioner, West participated directly in all significant decisions for the CFTC, including the designation of new markets, adoption of rules, commencement of enforcement actions, allocation of budget resources, ruling on appeals from Administrative Law Judges in customer reparation and enforcement cases, review of exchange disciplinary and emergency market actions, and maintaining industry oversight.
As a Commissioner, West also chaired the CFTC’s Advisory Committee on CFTC/State Coordination, served as CFTC delegate to the U.S. Office of Consumer Affairs Consumer Advisory Council chairing its Finance Group Task Force, and participated as a member of the National Futures Association Consumer Advisory Council. West was reappointed for another 5-years in 1987.
In 1992, when West’s second term expired, he continued to serve as a Commissioner until a replacement was named. From 1993-1995, he was Executive Director of the North American Securities Administrators Association, Inc. in Washington, D.C. From 1996 to the present, he has served as president of West & West in Alexandria, representing groups involved in preserving the Everglades ecosystem.
West married Anne Smith Paine of Valdosta, Georgia. They have three sons: Fowler West, Jr., Mitchell Paine West, and William Robert Poage West. He participated in the Baylor University Men and Women of Merit Week in 1984, and was the recipient of the Congressional Staffer of the Year award in 1977. From 2005-2016, he served as co-chair of the Standing Committee, a friend and fund-raising group for the W. R. Poage Legislative Library at Baylor University.
Scope and Content
The Fowler C. West papers range from 1964-2009 and cover the career of Fowler West in Washington, D.C. The papers document his service on the House Agriculture Committee and his tenure as a commissioner with the Commodity Futures Trading Commission. They are arranged in three series, including Agriculture Committee, Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), and Personal, with CFTC being the largest series.
Agriculture Committee materials span West’s employment on the staff of the House Committee and as staff director. Topics included in this series are budgets, subsidies, farm problems and farm bills, grain and fuel legislation, rural development, and travel. This series also contains travel materials from Agriculture Committee delegations to Africa, Central America, India, and Southeast Asia.
The Commodity Futures Trading Commission series includes eleven subseries. Following the General subseries, the Advisory Committee on CFTC-State Cooperation subseries contains materials documenting West’s chairmanship of the Federal Advisory Committee. Campaigns I and II subseries’ document West’s appointment to the CFTC in 1982. The Correspondence subseries is arranged chronologically. Dissents and Separate Views show the issues that were adjudicated to the level of the full Commission. The Meetings subseries has memos concerning business discussed at each commission meeting, notebooks for each quarter reporting on the staff, programs, statistics, and objectives of the CFTC, and memos from the CFTC’s Division of Enforcement, Division of Trading and Markets, and Division of Economic Analysis. News Clippings document national press coverage of West and the CFTC. The series also includes subseries' Publications, Memos, and Notes; and Speeches and Statements. The Subjects subseries contains all CFTC materials not filed with a particular committee meeting or with correspondence files. It is the largest subseries in the CFTC series.
The Personal series consists of items relating to Baylor University, biographical information, West’s promotions, invitations, and programs.
Arrangement
The Fowler C. West papers were originally processed in 1994 after a donation of 14 record storage boxes in 1993. Additions were added in 2013. They were previously arranged in 6 series: Personal Files, Agriculture Committee, CFTC Correspondence, CFTC Committee Meetings, CFTC Subject Files, and Publications. They are currently arranged in three series topically and chronologically: I. Agriculture Committee, II. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), and III. Personal. The West papers are in good condition.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to the W. R. Poage Legislative Library in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 93. Acquired 1993-02-17
Related Resources
Related references
Fowler C. West papers, Accession #93, Baylor Collections of Political Materials, W. R. Poage Legislative Library, Baylor University.
Yuen, Mike. “Wacoan Goes-Fer: Humble Start Leads to Federal Career.” Waco Tribune-Herald, May 27, 1979.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Poage, W. R. (William Robert), 1899-1987.; West, Fowler C.-- Archives.
Subjects (Organizations)
United States. Commodity Futures Trading Commission -- Officials and Employees.; United States. Congress. House. Committee on Agriculture--Officials and employees.
Subjects
Agriculture -- United States.; Commerce--United States.; Legislation--United States.; Rural development--United States.
Genres
Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Correspondence.; Invitations.; Memorandums.; Minutes (Records); Photographs.; Programs (Publications).; Records (Documents); Speeches.
- Agriculture Committee, 1964-1988; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Average.
  Biography/Profile
  The Agriculture Committee series covers West’s employment on the staff of the House Committee from 1965-1969, and again from 1971-1982. In 1973, he was promoted to staff director, representing the Chairman in scheduling and processing legislative matters and organizing the Committee each session. Topics included in this series are budgets, subsidies, farm problems and farm bills, grain and fuel legislation, rural development, and travel. This series also contains travel materials, including itineraries, maps, and notes from Agriculture Committee fact-finding delegations sent to Africa in 1964, Central America in 1966, India in 1966, and Southeast Asia in 1968. The travel subseries is arranged chronologically. This series is in good condition.
  - General, 1966-1988; 1
    - Capitol Report, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Federal ‘Love’ Lost on Loving County, 1970 April 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Farm Credit Act, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Rural Telephone Bank, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Rural Development, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Rural Development, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Southwest Missouri Resource Conservation and Development Project Area, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Nixon-Ford Negation of America’s Farmers, circa 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Committee Organization, 95th Congress, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Food Stamp Testimony, Louisiana Food and Nutrition Service, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Transition Planning Group Carter/Mondale, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Agricultural Land Trust Venture Congressional Hearings, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Omnibus Farm Bill, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Robert V. Rota, Correspondence Form, 1978 January 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Farm Summit Task Force, Agriculture and Government, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - National 4-H Council Citizenship Focus, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Rules Committee, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Agricultural Issues Forum of the Agriculture Council of America, 1979 June 4 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Fuel Facts, Oil Supplies and Prices, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - AAM - American Agriculture Movement, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Alabama Coushatta Tribes of Texas/Louisiana Relief, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Beekeeper Indemnity Termination, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Budget, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - China Grain Agreement, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Farm Credit Association, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Farm Organization Positions, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Farm Price and Credit Crisis, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Farm Program History since 1977, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Grain Companies, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Grain Embargo, Domestic, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Grain Exports Suspension, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Humane Horse Treatment Bill, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Palouse Basin Region, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Rice Program, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Sunflower Seed Exports, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Air Controller’s Strike, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Administrative Changes for the Staff, 1981 January 12 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Budget (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Budget (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Budget Crisis, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Committee on Agriculture Budget, 1981 June 17 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Committee Budget Resolution Preparation, 1981 February 6 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Committee Offices, 1981 February 12 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Conservation Credit Rural Development, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Dairy Price Support, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Deboned Meat, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Economy and Recession, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - European Economic Community Trade War, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Family Farms, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Farm Bill, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Farm Bill, Conference, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Farm Bill, Cotton-Rice-Sugar Subcommittee, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Farm Bill, Domestic Marketing Consumer Relations Nutrition, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Farm Bill, Floor Consideration, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Farm Bill, Hearings, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Farm Bill, Livestock, Dairy and Poultry, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Farm Bill, Operations, Research and Foreign Aid, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Farm Bill, Opposition, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Farm Bill Status, 1981 April 27 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Farm Bill Status, 1981 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Farm Bill Status, Senate, 1981 July 8 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Farm Bill, Tobacco and Peanuts, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Farmers and Tax Bill, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Food and Agriculture Act, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Food for Peace Cargo Preference, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Congressional Soc/Staff Club, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Food Stamp Program, Reconciliation Conference, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Gasohol, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Grain Exports, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Grain Policy, US-USSR, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Gypsy Moths, Republican Dissents, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - House Rules and Agenda, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Impoundment Powers of the President, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Legislative Process, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Mediterranean Fruit Fly, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Meeting on Oversight, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Members of the Majority Committee Staff, 1981 February 4 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Milk and Casein Price Support, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Party Unity, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Peanut Program, Senate Action, 1981 September 17 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Pesticides, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - President’s Economic Program, “Reagan’s Economic Mess”, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Research Project, 1981 May 12 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Room Reservations, House Office Buildings, Garages and Capitol Power Plant, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - School Lunch, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Senate Agriculture Committee Members, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Social Security System, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Staff Expenses, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Staff Travel and Field Hearings, 1981 March 16 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - State Department, US Sugar Policy, 1981 July 7 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Subcommittee Meeting Preparation, 1981 March 9 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Subcommittee Staff Salaries, 1981 July 10 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Sugar Policy, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Telephone Program History, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Tobacco, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - USDA Meeting, Butter Sale to New Zealand, 1981 July 10 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Wheat, Soybeans and Feed Grains, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Wheat Organizations, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Appropriations Bills, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Budget (1 of 3), 1982 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Budget (2 of 3), 1982 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Budget (3 of 3), 1982 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Budget, Balanced Resolution, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Budget Reconciliation Press Release, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Butter Sale New Zealand, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Farm Economy, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Farm Problems, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Foley Response to Reagan Tax Bill, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Grain Announcement, 1982 October (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Grain Exports Suspension, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Meat Grading, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Peanuts, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Tax Increase, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Wheat Program, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Predator Control, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Trips, 1964-1980; 2
    - Africa, Department of State Background Material, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Africa, Itinerary, 1964 November 15-December 5 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Africa, Notes [Fowler West], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Africa, Rep. D.R. Matthews Newsletter, 1965 January 8 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Central America, Agricultural Commodities Imported from the US, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Central America, Conference Proceedings, 1966 May 11-17 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Central America, Itinerary, 1966 May (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Central America, Photographs, Textbook Development Center, 1966 May (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Central America, Notes [Fowler West], 1966 May (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Central America, Receipts, 1966 May (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Central American, Trip Legislation-H.R. 833, 1966 April (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - India, India Map, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - India, Menu (see oversized), 1966 December 2 (Box 4, Folder 25A)
    - India, Notes [by Fowler West], 1966 December (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - India, Photographs, 1966 December (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - India, Hyde Murray Drawing Indira Gandhi, 1966 December (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - India, Food for India, Dole-Poage Press Release, 1967 February 2 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - India, Food for India, Legislation- H.J. Res 267-P.L. 90-7, 1967 March-April (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - India, Food for India, Poage Statement, 1967 February 28 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - India, Grain Grant Request, 1967 January 11 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Southeast Asia, Agriculture Committee Justification, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Southeast Asia, Background Material, “The A.I.D. Program in Vietnam”, 1967 July (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Southeast Asia, Background Material, US Military Assistance Command Vietnam, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Southeast Asia, Correspondence, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Southeast Asia, Food Aid-P.L. 480, Rice, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Southeast Asia, Food Aid-P.L. 480, Title I Situation, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Southeast Asia, Food Aid-P.L. 480, Title II Food for Freedom, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Southeast Asia, Food Aid-P.L. 480, Vietnam & USDA, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Southeast Asia, Itinerary, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Southeast Asia, Maps, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Southeast Asia, Notes [Fowler West], 1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Venezuela, Notebook, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Venezuela, Photographs, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Africa, General, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), 1975-1993; 2
  The Commodity Futures Trading Commission series has eleven subseries and includes background research, correspondence, cases, news clippings, articles, speeches, and legislative proposals. Further description is provided with each subseries.
  - General, 1980-1992; 1
    The General subseries contains appointments and general files related to the CFTC.
    - Appointments, 1980-1992 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Clinton Transition, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Geoffrey Aronow, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - CFTC and SEC Merger, 1990 March (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - CFTC Historical Gallery, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - CFTC Report to Task Group on Regulation of Financial Services, 1983 March 23 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Stock Market Crash of 1987, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Wendy L. Gramm, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Advisory Committee on CFTC-State Cooperation, 1983-1992; 2
    The Advisory Committee on CFTC-State Cooperation subseries documents West’s chairmanship of the Federal Advisory Committee through speeches and information on topics such as commodity pools and model state commodity code. The committee addressed various anti-fraud initiatives involving federal and state enforcement efforts, and bank financed precious metal transactions. West urged the Advisory Committee to address the federal problems of deregulation.
    - General, 1983-1992; 1
      - Appointments, Fowler West, 1983-1986 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Article, “CFTC and States Join Forces to Fight Commodity-Like Fraud”, 1985 January (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Commodity Law Violators’ Manual, 1984 January (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Meeting, Commission/States and North American Securities Administrators Association, 1983 December 6 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1983 March 24 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1984 May 8 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1986 June 24 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1986 July 24 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1987 February 5 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1987 February 7 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Meetings Minutes, 1987 October 8 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1988 September 14 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1989 April 11 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1989 November 14 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1991 February 21 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1991 February 21 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1991 November 21 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1992 May 12 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Members, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Resolution of Support, National Futures Association, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Bank Financed Precious Metal Transactions, 1987-1992; 2
      - Bank Notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - CTA Registration of 85-2 Dealers, 1989 September (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Current and Possible Regulatory Requirements and Compliance Activities, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - FDIC Report of Valley State Bank, Encino, California, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - FOIA Request on 85-2 Programs, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Monex, 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - News Clippings, 1987-1992 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - North American Securities Administrators (NASAA), 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Off-Exchange Task Force, Committee Recommendations, 1988 January 27 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Off-Exchange Task Force, Interpretative Letter of 85-2, 1988 July 11 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Off-Exchange Task Force, Statement, Fowler C. West, 1987 June 9 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - Off-Exchange Task Force, Summary Report, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Program Transactions, 1985-1988 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Publication, “Bank Financed Precious Metals Trading-Is It Just Another Precious Metals Scam?” William Lafferty, Dickinson Law Review, Vol. 93, No. 1, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Transactions, California- Arrington, Spencer, and Associates, 1989 June (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Transactions, California- Guardian Trust Bank Finance Program, 1988 June (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Transactions, California- Precious Metals Finance Corporation, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Transactions, Florida- Bachus and Stratton, Inc., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Transactions, Florida- Guardian Trust Co., 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Transactions, Florida- SafraBank, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Transactions, Florida- Uni-Vest Financial Services, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Commodity Pools, 1983-1991; 3
      - Article, “Regulation of Commodity Pool Operators Under the Commodity Exchange Act,” Jeffery Rosen, Washington and Lee Law Review, Vol. 40, No. 3, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - North American Securities Administration Association (NASAA) Guidelines, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Proposal, “To Simplify Commodity Pool Disclosure Documents,” Managed Futures Association, 1991 June (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Regulation of Commodity Pools, August 1988 (Box 7, Folder 14)